<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pkgmetadata SYSTEM "https://www.gentoo.org/dtd/metadata.dtd">
<pkgmetadata>
  <longdescription lang="en">
    XMRigCC is a high performance, open source, cross platform RandomX, GhostRider, KawPow, CryptoNight
    unified CPU/GPU miner. Official binaries are available for Windows, Linux, freebsd, macOS and Android.
    
    XMRigCC is a XMRig fork which adds remote control and monitoring functions to XMRigCC miners. It lets you control your miners via a Dashboard or the REST api.
    XMRigCC has a "Command and Control" (CC) server part, a daemon to keep the XMRigCC miner alive and modifications to send the current status to the CC Server.
    The modified version can handle commands like "update config", "start/stop mining" or "restart/shutdown/reboot" which can be send from the CC-Server Dashboard.
    Assign config templates to multiple miners with a single click and let them switch configs without connecting to each of them.
    Watch your miners logs with the simple remote Log viewer and monitor you miners. When the hashrate drops or one of your miners went offline you can get a notification via
    PushOver or Telegram automatically so that you dont need to watch your miners all day. 
</longdescription>
  <use>
    <flag name="cuda">
      Build cuda plugin
    </flag>
    <flag name="ccclient">
      Enable "Command and Control" (CC) Client features
    </flag>
    <flag name="ccclientexec">
      Enable "Command and Control" (CC) Client shell execution (shell execution might be a security risk)
    </flag>
    <flag name="ccserver">
      Enable "Command and Control" (CC) Server features
    </flag>
    <flag name="donate">
      Set the default donation level to 5% instead of 0%
    </flag>
    <flag name="http">
      Enable built in HTTP support, this feature is used for HTTP API and daemon (solo mining) support
    </flag>
    <flag name="hwloc">
      Use <pkg>sys-apps/hwloc</pkg> for CPU affinity support
    </flag>
    <flag name="opencl">
      Enable OpenCL support
    </flag>
  </use>
  <upstream>
    <remote-id type="github">Bendr0id/xmrigCC</remote-id>
  </upstream>
</pkgmetadata>
